solimba.com 2015-03-18

# Privacy Policy - Solimba

Solimba protects and guarantees security in the collection and processing of the data that is effected through this site as well as the strict compliance with the current policy with regards to data protection. The following paragraphs inform about our procedures of data collection and processing.

Through this website personal data will be collected with the purposes of managing and providing our services, sending internal commercial promotions and providing information of interest for users, related the services of the site.

These data are stored in a archive of personal data whose Solimba is holder, properly registered at the Agency of Data Protection. 

Nevertheless, the data holder may communicate his/her intention not to be sent any more information at any moment, by sending en email to support@solimba.com. 

Solimba warranties the application of all those safety measures , required by the current data protection legislation, to all personal data collected, being these stored with strict confidentiality and in places where access, misuse, manipulation, alteration,damage orlossby third parties is prevented.

Solimba, compliantly with the provisions of the Organic Law of Data Protection and in its Development Regulation, commits not to effect any sale or transfer of these data to third parties neither to use or treat data with any purposenother than those indicated.

Solimba uses cookies in order to enable the Company to provide its users with a better service, including interest-based advertising. Users can configure their internet browser to alert them to the reception of cookies, thus affording them the possibility of deciding whether to accept the cookies in question or not.

Likewise the user will be kept informed about the possibility to exercise, at any moment, the rights of access, amendment, cancellation and opposition recognized by the regulation by sending a written request to the Responsible of Solimba Archive to support@solimba.com

##  Identification and contact data of the Company

Solimba Aplicaciones S.L. is a Spanish company based in Badalona (Barcelona) Avenida Maresme 44-46 2a 26, registered in the Chamber of Commerce, book 42.011, folder 0036, sheet 398987, with registration number (CIF) B65373938.

**Terms of use and Privacy Policy** \- Should users wish to file any complaints, they can contact the company through the support form available in the site or sending a message to the email address support@solimba.com.
